Are you looking at naked tribeswomen?
벌거벗은 원주민 여자 보니?
아냐, 봐
No, look.
That's a pig.
돼지잖아
I know.
But look at the knobs on it!
알아, 이 아랫도리를 봐
- 왔니?
- 어서 와
Emily's cousin kicked me out.
에밀리 사촌한테 쫓겨났다
-What?
-Why?
- 뭐?
- 왜?
마누라 사촌한테 빌린 집인데
이혼을 하게 됐다
When you sublet
from your wife's cousin...
...then you divorce, sometimes
the cousin wants his apartment back.
그럼 그 사촌은 갑자기
아파트를 돌려 받고 싶겠지?
Didn't you sign a lease?
계약서 같은 건 안 썼냐?
가족끼리 계약서는 무슨!
Who needs a lease when it's "family"?
야, 우리랑 있자
You can stay with us.
- 그래도 괜찮아
- 그럼, 당연하지
Anything you need.
아무래도 좋지만
But you have to let us know
when you feel better...
기분 좋아지면 즉시 말해
너 머리 좀 놀려보게
...so we can make fun of your hair.
- 봤구나
- 그럼
You got it.
Thanks, I really appreciate this.
I'm going to get packing again.
고마워서 어쩌냐
난 가서 또 짐 싸야겠다
요즘 이사를 너무 많이 다녀서
꼭 유목민이 된 것 같네
I've been moving around so much
that I feel like a nomad.
-What?
-He thought you said gonad.
왜?
얜 '유방민'으로 들었어
The One Where Ross Moves ln
If every place were this clean,
it'd be tough making a living.
와우, 레스토랑이 다
이렇게 깨끗하다면
전 먹고 살기 힘들겠군요
Oh, Larry!
오, 래리
위생과 사람들은
커미션을 받고 일하나요?
Do health inspectors
work on commission?
No, bribes.
아뇨, 뇌물이죠
웃어도 괜찮죠?
-It's okay to laugh?
-I was just kidding.
- 네, 농담이니까
- 그래요
-I'll check the kitchen floor.
-Knock yourself out.
- 주방 바닥을 볼까요?
- 네, 맘껏 보세요
I don't get violations.
You could eat beans off that floor.
규정위반은 없어요
콩도 주워 먹을 정도죠
But don't, because that'd be a violation.
하지만 먹지 마세요
그건 규정위반이니까
맛나겠다
Yummy!
래리?
그래, 우리 주방 바닥도
봐달라고 해야지
Yeah, I'd let him check out
my kitchen floor.
A ninety-eight.
98점입니다
2점 뺐어요, 주방장 모자를
안 쓴 건 제5조 위반입니다
I deducted two points
for not wearing your hat.
That is a Section 5 violation.
갑자기 왜 이러실까
Now look, Larry, honey.
I wrote the book on Section 5.
전 제5조에 대해 책도 썼는데
주방 밖에선 쓸 필요 없어요
You only need to wear it
in the kitchen.
모자 어디 있죠?
-Where's your hat?
-ln the kitchen. I'll get it.
주방에요, 가져올게요
그래서 2점 뺀 겁니다
There's the two points!
네가 쓴 책 읽어봐야겠다
You should really read
that book you wrote.
모자를 쓰려면 주방에 들어가야
한다는 걸 알고 있었군요
You saw the hat in the kitchen and
knew she'd go in hatless to get it.
You could have your own
health inspector detective show.
위생과 형사 하셔도 되겠다
그건 잘 모르겠군요
I don't know about that.
전 똘마니 분다 할게요
But then I could be
your sidekick, Voonda.
분다의 전화번호를 알면
언제 저녁이나 함께 할 텐데
Maybe I could ask Voonda
to dinner sometime?
걔도 좋아할 거예요
She would love that...
깨끗한 식당은 다 아시니까
...since you know
all the clean places to eat.
- 전화 드리죠
- 좋아요
I'll call you.
너무 재미있다
He's so funny!
Thank you.
고마워요
모니카, 로스는 어때?
에밀리 일은 괜찮나?
How's Ross doing
since all the Emily stuff?
He's not great.
별로 좋진 않지만
극복하는 중이야
But he's dealing with it.
Wait, you're not
잠깐, 너 혹시...
됐어, 나도 다시
시작하고 싶진 않아
I can't get started
with all that Ross stuff again.
He'll be screwed up for a long time.
한동안은 힘들 거야
게다가 방금 이혼한 남자를
내가 왜 건드리니?
Besides, I don't go for guys
right after they get divorced.
맞아, 결혼 직전의
남자만 건드리지
Right, you only go for them
five minutes before they get married.
모카 자바 2파운드요
-Two pounds of mocha java.
-It's Danny.
대니잖아
두 사람 다시 안 만나?
Are you going to go out again?
모르겠어
그 뒤로는 전화도 없어
I don't know.
He hasn't called since we went out.
복도에서 만나면
장난은 치지, 이렇게...
I see him in the hallway.
We flirt. I'm all:
And then nothing.
그게 다야
- 안녕
- 안녕, 대니
Wow, thirsty.
갈증나요?
토요일에 집에서 파티가
있어서요, 집들이 겸해서
I'm having a party on Saturday.
Sort of a housewarming thing.
- 좋겠네요
- 멋지다
-Fun.
-Great!
- 기다려지는군요
- 네
I'm looking forward to it.
그럼 또 봐요
See you!
우린 집들이 못 가는구나
So I guess we won't
be warming his house.
그래, 이제야 감이 잡히네
All right, I see what he's doing.
나더러 자기한테 데이트
신청하라는 뜻이야
He's not asking me out
because he wants me to ask him out.
- 안 할 거야?
- 당연하지
And you won't do that.
That's right!
Because that would give him
the control.
주도권을 잡자는 거야
파티가 있다고 하면 내가 뭐
초대해달라고 애원이라도 해?
So now he comes up with this
"I've got a party" thing...
...to get me to hint
for an invitation.
Blew up in his face, didn't it?
면전에서 퇴짜를 놔버렸지
So there is no party?
- 파티는 없다는 거야?
- 아니지
No, there's a party.
There's a party.
파티는 있어
파티는 있다고
But the power?
하지만 파워의 행방은
오리무중이야
That is still up for grabs.
You follow me?
알아듣겠어?
대충은
I think so.
파티에 초대 안 한 건
널 좋아해서다?
So he won't invite you to his party
because he likes you?
Exactly!
예리했어
Then why didn't he invite me?
그럼 난 왜 초대 안 했지?
오! 내가 따라갈까 봐
To throw me off.
로스?
Hey, roomies!
- 안녕, 룸메이트?
- 그래
I love what you've done
with the place.
잘해놨다
I know it's a lot of boxes.
알아, 상자가 좀 많지
같이 있게 해줘서 정말 고맙다
-I appreciate you letting me stay here.
-Not a problem.
별말씀을
Since you'll be here a while...
그리고 한동안 있을 거니까
응답기에 네 이름도 남겨 둬
...we could put your name
on the answering machine.
I hope you don't mind...
이래도 되는지 모르지만
벌써 내가 손을 써뒀어
...but I kind of already
jazzed it up a little.
Check it out.
들어봐
우리가 우리가
전화 드리죠
We will
We will call you back
좋은데
Pretty cool.
- 근사하지?
- 그래
- 너도 가짜로 웃는 거지?
- 눈물은 진짜야
-You're fake laughing too, right?
-The tears are real.
You look beautiful this evening.
정말 아름다우시군요
Show me the badge again.
배지 또 보여줘요
Shiny.
눈부셔요
손 좀 씻고 올게요
퇴근하고 오는 길이라
You mind if I wash up?
Who knows where these have been?
얘들이 염려스럽군요
You are just nonstop!
정말 끝이 없으시네요
-We're out of here.
-Why?
- 나갑시다
- 왜요?
주방에서 규정위반을
열 건이나 발견했어요
I saw 1 0 violations.
I'm shutting this place down!
폐업시키겠어요
-You have the power to do that?
-This does.
- 그럴 힘이 있나요?
- 얘한테 있죠
Shut it down.
폐업시키세요
왔냐?
What are you doing?
뭐하냐?
Nothing.
아무 것도
You built a fort, didn't you?
요새를 만들었구나
Kind of.
아네
Oh, my God! The air purifier.
Ross' air purifier.
맙소사
로스의 공기청정기잖아
All I heard for four years
through college was....
대학 4년 동안
이 소리만 들었어
You should have gone out
once in a while.
가끔 외출도 하지
-I hate this thing!
-Come on, Chandler.
나 이거 싫어
그러지 마라
로스는 친구야
Ross is our friend.
He needs us right now.
지금은 우리가 필요해
So why don't you be a grownup
and come watch TV in the fort?
어른답게 요새에 와서
TV나 보는 게 어때
Can't believe that Larry closed down
Churman's. I love that place.
처먼스를 폐쇄시키다니
난 거기 좋던데
You should have heard
about all their violations.
하지만 위반사항이 너무 많대
Larry said that they should call it Vermin's.
래리는 그 집을
'더러먼스'로 부르래
That guy just plain kills me.
사람을 잡는다니까
어서 와요, 대니
I wanted to invite you to the party.
내일 밤 파티에
와줬으면 하구요
고마워요, 꼭 갈게요
Thanks, I'll try to stop by.
난 좀 바쁠 것 같은데
Actually, I think
I'm going to be busy.
You are?
바빠?
그래
Remember, I've got that gala?
그 축제 잊었어?
무슨 축제죠?
What's the gala for?
그게... 보트놀이 축제요
It's a regatta gala.
Do you sail?
정말요? 배를 타나요?
No, but I support it.
타는 건 아니고 후원을 하죠
그렇군요
I hope I see you tomorrow night.
Take care.
- 그럼 내일 봐요
- 그래요
- 갈게요
- 네
Walked right into that one,
didn't he?
제대로 걸려들었군
What one?
걸려들다니
You wanted him to invite you
and he did.
원하던 대로 초대를 받았잖아
He waited until the last minute.
So if I said yes...
마지막까지 기다려야지
허접한 파티에 초대한다고
기다렸다는 듯 응할까?
...he'd know I had nothing better
to do than wait for his invitation.
But I said no...
단호히 거절했어, 그래서
운전석은 내 차지가 됐지
...which puts me back
in the driver's seat.
So the ball is in his court?
그래서 공은 저쪽으로
넘어갔다?
Ball?
공? 공 같은 건 없어
No, there's no ball.
Hey, Phoebe, you want to join us?
피비, 이거 좀 먹을래?
-Oh, sure, yeah. Where is this from?
-It's from Sun Ling's.
그래, 어디서 샀는데?
선링스
Oh, Larry just told me
something about Sun Ling.
래리가 선링스에 대해
뭐라고 했는데
Oh, no, thank you.
아니, 됐다
Joey, please.
부탁 좀 하자
Sorry.
미안
Hello, children.
안녕, 얘들아
어서 와, 푸스볼이나 할까?
부탁이다
You want to play some foosball?
Please?
- 좋아
- 거기가 아냐
We moved the table into my room
because of all the boxes.
테이블 내 방으로 옮겼어
이 상자들 때문에...
Come on!
빨랑!
I have one question.
좋아, 하나만 묻자
What is the deal with this?
이게 대체 뭐냐?
Bye-bye, little puppet Joey hand?
빠이빠이, 인형 부리는
조이의 손아?
아니, 조용히 하라는 것 말이야
No, the quiet down thing.
그럼 이거겠지
You mean this.
I don't know how much more
I can take.
어디까지 참아야 되지?
Did you know he taped over my Baywatch
tape with a show about bugs?
녀석이 내 베이워치 테이프에다
벌레 프로그램 녹화한 거 알아?
My God!
내가 돈다
What if that had been porn?
포르노였으면 어쩔 뻔했어
All right, this may be tough...
야, 힘들겠지만 로스잖아
난 대학생활도 함께 했는걸
...but it's Ross.
I survived college with him.
I guess I can hold out
a little longer.
알았어
좀 더 참아보지 뭐
Let's have a game.
- 게임이나 하자
- 그래
그렇지!
Fellas?
친구들아?
So he's out of here.
역시 내보내야겠다
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Got anything to eat?
I went to Jono's and it was closed.
먹을 거 있어? 치킨 사려고
조노스에 갔더니 문 닫았더라
I took Larry there, but it was all
violated, so we shut it down.
래리랑 거기 갔다 위반사항이
너무 많아서 폐쇄시켜 버렸어
If this guy keeps closing our
favorite places, where will we eat?
단골가게를 다 폐쇄시키면
우린 어디서 먹어?
글쎄, 깨끗한 식당?
I don't know. Clean places?
그래, 군침 돈다
Yum!
It's Danny.
대니야
Don't let him in!
I'm supposed to be at a gala.
못 들어오게 해
난 보트놀이 간 거야
We'll be right there.
Can't you say it's later?
기다려요
이따가 시작한다고 해
What kind of a regatta gala
starts at night?
무슨 보트놀이가
밤에 시작을 하나
The fake kind.
가짜 보트놀이
저기, 국자 있으면
하나 빌릴까요?
-I need a ladle. You got a ladle?
-We have a ladle.
국자야 있죠
- 고마워요, 파티에서 봐요
- 그래요
See you at the party.
얘들아, 래리가 뭐랬냐면
'국자로 묵자'
You know what Larry would say?
He'd say, "See you ladle."
난 다 읽었는데 너도 볼래?
I'm done. You want anything?
Sports? International?
스포츠, 국제
아파트 매물?
Apartment listings?
- 스포츠로 줘
- 내 거야
I'll take sports.
Mine!
- 좋아, 그럼 국제면
- 그것도 내 거
All right, international.
That's mine too.
난 이태리 사람이잖아
I'm ltalian.
아파트 정보나 볼까?
쓸만한 건 없겠지만
I could check apartment listings,
though there's never anything here.
7면에도 없어?
Not even on page seven?
그래, 맞아
You're right.
Here's an affordable place.
가격도 적당한 듯하고
침실 둘에 직장 근처
Two-bedroom, close to work.
It's available in five weeks.
5주 후에 빈다는데?
동그라미 친 건 어때?
What about that circled one?
글쎄, 원룸치고는 좀 비싸다
It's kind of expensive for a studio.
당장 입주할 수 있네
But it's available now.
- 그렇지?
- 아무렴
Isn't it?
Yes, it is.
가서 한번 보자
Let's go look at it!
- 알았어, 가자
- 잘 생각했어
There we go!
청정기 필터 사야 되는데
너희들도 좀 보태라
Guys, would you chip in for some
new air filters for the purifier?
어차피 같이 쓰는 거니까
I mean, after all,
we are all using it.
- 빨랑 가자
- 그래
Let's go quicker!
이런!
Oh, my God!
이 주방을 봐
Look at this kitchen/bathroom.
더하기 욕실
멋지다, 욕조 안에서
요리도 할 수 있으니까
That's great!
So you can cook while in the tub.
요즘 사람들 머리 좋아
Somebody was using his head.
다른 데도 둘러봐야지
Let's check out
the rest of the place.
이게 전부 같은데?
I think this is it.
아냐, 여긴 좀 그렇다
I don't know.
Maybe we should keep looking.
그래도 비어 있잖아
But this place is available now.
5주 동안 우리랑 지낼 거야?
You don't want to be stuck
with us for five weeks.
여길 얻으란 말이야?
So you think I should
take this place?
완벽하네
It's perfect!
넌 어때?
How about you?
주방 더하기 욕실
Kitchen, slash, bathroom.
무슨 말인지 알겠다
I see what you guys are saying.
내려가서 신청서 쓰자
I'll go downstairs
and fill out an application.
우린 나쁜 놈들이야
We are bad people.
우리 속셈을 알고 있어
왜 모르겠어!
He knew we were trying
to get rid of him.
우리도 주방에 욕조 들여놔?
Could we get a bathtub
in our kitchen?
나갈 준비됐나요?
Ready for dinner?
- 그럼요
- 좋아요
-Absolutely.
-Great.
블리커 스트리트의
이태리 식당은 어때요
You wanted to go to
the ltalian place on Bleecker St.?
거기 참 좋은데...
I love that place!
그니까 안 돼요
So, no.
- 마마 리제티스는?
- 으엑...
How about Mama Lozetti's?
좋아요
Sure.
우유를 저렇게 내놨네
How long has that milk
been sitting out?
아뇨, 여긴 정말 깨끗해요
No, this place is totally healthy.
이 우유는 내 거예요
This milk is mine.
I bought this today...
오늘 내가 샀어요
우유 마시고 싶어서
...because I was thirsty for milk,
you know?
이제 갈까요?
Okay, let's go.
이봐요
Hey, buddy.
위생법 11조 B항에 따라서
모든 쓰레기는 뒤로 내가야죠
Health Code 1 1 B requires that refuse
be taken out the back exit.
그럼 세탁소를
돌아가야 해서요
But then I have to go
all the way around.
위생보다 편리함이
우선이란 말이오?
So you choose convenience
over health?
Would you be interested in a free coffee?
피곤하실 텐데
커피 한 잔 드려요?
그만해요, 래리...
Stop, Larry.
Can't you just be Larry and not
Larry the health inspector guy?
좀 평범해질 순 없어요?
위생과 직원 래리 말구요
It was exciting at first.
처음엔 재미있었지만
지금은 외식할 데가 없네요
But now, it's like, so where
are we going to eat ever?
I suppose I could give him a warning.
이번엔 경고로 끝내겠소
Thank you.
고마워요
Go, go!
알았으면 빨리 가요
저녁 먹고 누군가
혼내주고 싶다면
If, after dinner,
you still need to bust someone...
...I know a hot dog vendor
who picks his nose.
코 후비는 핫도그 장사 알아요
Maybe we did good,
helping Ross get back on his feet.
어떻게 생각하면 로스가
자립하도록 도와준 거잖아
That was a nice place.
- 그래, 집 괜찮더라
- 그럼
No closet space, but he could hang
his stuff out the window in a bag.
수납공간은 좀 부족하지만
창문 밖으로 걸어놓으면 되지
맞아
What do we do?
- 이제 어떡하지?
- 글쎄
I don't know.
Maybe pizza?
피자 먹을까?
About Ross!
로스 말이야
여보세요?
네
It's the apartment manager.
Ross put us as references.
아파트 관리인이야
우릴 보증인으로 기록했대
로스 정말 괜찮은 친구죠
네, 아주 믿을 만하고...
Ross is the greatest guy.
He's very reliable
Of course, he has a big, huge dog
that barks into the night.
황소 만한 개를 키우는데
밤새 짖어댄답니다
Well, who doesn't love dogs?
개 싫어하는 사람 없죠
He's a tap dancer.
그 친구 탭 댄서예요
Yes, some would say
that is a lost art.
물론 한물 간 예술로
보는 사람도 있죠
He's a pimp!
포주예요
There you go. He's a pimp.
그렇죠, 포주 맞아요
He's a big, tap-dancing pimp!
탭댄스 하는 포주
여보셔?
그래, 준비됐어
-Okay, honey, I'm ready.
-What are you doing?
뭐 하는 거야?
I am going to wander into the party
and I will be all, you know:
파티에 가려고
보트놀이에서 무심코
돌아오는 사람처럼
"l don't need this,
I'm coming from a regatta gala."
Did you get this out of a book?
책에서 읽은 거니?
Monica, honey, this is as real as it gets.
모니카, 이보다 더
현실일 순 없어
This is never going to work.
He's right there.
일 틀어지겠다
저기 있어
가서 인사해
Just go say hi.
보트놀이 다녀오는 것처럼
아래층에서 올라와야 돼
I have to go downstairs and back up,
as if I'm coming home from the gala.
가서 주의 좀 끌어
So just go distract him.
But don't be sexy.
섹시하지 않게
- 안녕, 대니?
- 왔어요? 어때요?
What's going on?
멋진 파티네요
음식도 훌륭하고
This is a great party.
Great food.
대부분 파티는 칩이랑
살사 소스가 전부인데
You know, most parties, it's all
chips and salsa, chips and salsa.
근데...
So....
이건 뭐죠?
What's this?
샐러드요
Salad.
그럼 이건?
And what's this?
빵
Bread.
요리사 아니세요?
Aren't you a chef?
- 안녕, 레이첼
- 안녕하세요
그러고 보니 오늘이 파티군요
Right, tonight was your party.
You look great!
I'm glad you made it.
멋진데요
늦지 않아서 다행이네요
알다시피 보트놀이도
언젠가는 끝이 나죠
Well, you know,
the gala had to end sometime.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
어디 가지 말아요
금방 올게요
네, 알았어요
Whose court is the ball in now?
자, 이제 공이
어느 쪽에 있지?
I thought there wasn't a ball.
공 같은 건 없다며
Come on. He's glad I came.
He doesn't want me to go anywhere.
왜 이래, 좋아서
날 붙잡는 거 봐
Ball's flying all over the place.
천지에 공 날아다닌다
This is my friend, Tom.
내 친구 탐이에요
This is the girl I told you about.
이쪽은 내가 말한 그 아가씨
이런, 내 얘기를 하고
다니는군요
Come on!
You telling people about me?
I think you two
could really hit it off.
둘이 잘 맞을 거예요
난 가볼게
I'm gonna go mingle.
So you work at Bloomingdale's?
My mom calls it "Bloomies."
블루밍데일에 계신다고요?
우리 엄마는
'블루미'라고 하시죠
네, 좋아요
쉬어, 병사
At ease, soldier!
I'm sorry?
뭐라구요?
괜찮으니까 사실대로 말해요
난 다 아니까
You can just drop the act.
I know what's going on.
You're Danny's wingman, right?
대니의 바람잡이죠?
멋진 우정이에요
피 끓는 우애!
You guys are best buds, frat bros.
I'm going to go talk to a friend.
친구들한테 가볼게요
Yeah, you go talk to your friend.
네, 그 친구한테 전해요
Go tell him, "Nice try."
시도는 좋았다고
He just keeps lobbing them up...
어때, 로브로 올린 공을
장외로 쳐내버렸어
...and I keep knocking them
right out of the park.
I think I need a drink.
- 술이나 한잔하자
- 좋지
Ninety-eight...
...ninety-nine...
그리고 100
...one hundred!
Okay. Go.
됐어, 가
Dude, I'm telling you, I'm fine.
괜찮다고 했잖아
Here we go, here we go.
어허, 진정해
- 왔어?
- 그래
So I didn't get that apartment.
Some problem with my application.
그 아파트 얻기는 글렀다
신청서에 문제가 있었나 봐
You're kidding?
- 그럴 리가!
- 무슨 소리야
But Phoebe said I could stay
at her place for a while, so....
하지만 다행히 피비가
자기 집에 있어도 좋대
Well, you can't stay with Phoebe.
We're roomies.
뭐? 피비랑 있겠다니
우린 룸메이트야
You don't need me
taking up all your space.
나 때문에 불편하잖아
공간도 비좁고
We got plenty of space.
There's still some by that speaker.
공간은 많아, 아직 저쪽
스피커 옆에도 비었고
- 가지 마라
- 그래
Please, just stay.
Are you sure?
- 진심이야?
- 당연하지
-Definitely.
-You have to stay.
물론이야, 같이 있자
- 알았다
- 그렇지
So I'm a pimp, huh?
내가 포주라고?
It's okay.
괜찮아
내가 가끔은 좀 까다롭지만
불편하면 그렇다고 얘기를 해
Sometimes I can be a pain in the ass.
But just talk to me.
Tell me if something bothers you.
And I'll do everything I can
to keep my annoying habits just....
나도 최선을 다해볼 테니까
신경 거슬리는 버릇은 약간만...
Well, I see you've had
a very productive day.
대단히 유익한 하루였구나
The cowboy hat's a little much.
카우보이모자는
좀 과하지 않냐?
왜, 재미있는데
Come on, it's fun!
All right.
좋았어
Isn't this a woman's hat?
이건 여성용 모자 아냐?
쓸데없는 소리 말고
차나 끓여 와
Stop talking crazy, and make us tea!